Guide to the D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles archives, 1929-1995 and undated RL.00314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles, 1985-1989 and undated, 6 boxes
  - Pictures, 1985-1986
    - Meetings (Box DMB&B 6)
      - 1987, Apr., DMB&B Worldwide Management meeting (Box DMB&B 6)
    - Merger
      - Bloomfield Hills, Mich., holiday party, 1985, Dec. 17 (Box DMB&B 6)
      - Bloomfield Hills charities committee donation, 1985, Dec (Box DMB&B 6)
      - Chicago holiday/merger party, 1985, Nov.-Dec (Box DMB&B 6)
      - New York holiday/merger party, 1985, Nov. 25 (Box DMB&B 6)
      - New York staff, 1985, Nov. 25 (Box DMB&B 6)
      - San Francisco holiday party, 1985(?) (Box DMB&B 6)
      - Various locations: celebrations, 1985, Nov.-Dec (Box DMB&B 6)
      - Various locations: holiday/merger celebrations, 1985, Nov.-Dec (Box DMB&B 6)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Breakfast with the Networks, ABC, 1986, Jan. 22 (Box DMB&B 6)
      - San Francisco office, undated (Box DMB&B 6)
- Advertisements, 1932-1995
  General Foods is the client for which the most extensive corpus of material exists; the Procter & Gamble Company is represented in the second largest corpus of advertisements. Other clients with extensive amounts of material include: Allied Chemical Corporation, AVCO Manufacturing Company and its Crosley Division, Best Foods, the Colgate-Palmolive-Peet Company, the Florida Citrus Commission, International Business Machines (IBM), and West Point Pepperell. Benton & Bowles house advertisements are also included. Many items are fragile, some having been damaged by glue used to mount them in scrapbooks. Arranged alphabetically by the name of the client. See also oversize materials.
  - Allied Chemical Corporation (See also Oversize box OV1)
    - 1959-1960, Consumer magazine (Box 1)
    - 1959, Trade magazine (Box 1)
    - 1959-1960, Trade magazine (Box 1)
    - 1960-1961, Consumer magazine (Box 1)
    - 1960-1964, Consumer newspaper (Box 1)
    - 1960, Trade magazine (Box 1)
    - 1960-1961, Trade magazine (Box 1)
    - 1961-1962, Consumer magazine (Box 1)
    - 1961, Trade magazine, 4 folders (Box 1)
    - 1961-1962, Trade magazine (Box 1)
    - 1961-1962, Trade newspaper (Box 1)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - 1962-1963, Consumer magazine (Box 2)
    - 1962, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 2)
    - 1962, Trade newspaper (Box 2)
    - 1963, Consumer magazine (Box 2)
    - 1963-1964, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 2)
    - 1963, Trade magazine (Box 2)
    - 1964, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - 1964-1965, Consumer magazine (Box 2)
    - 1964-1966, Consumer magazine (Box 2)
    - 1964, Trade magazine, 1 of 4 folders (Box 2)
    - 1964, Trade magazine, 2-4 of 4 folders (Box 3)
    - 1964, Trade newspaper (Box 3)
    - 1965, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - 1965, Trade magazine, 4 folders (Box 3)
    - 1965-1966, Trade magazine (Box 3)
    - 1965-1966, Trade newspaper (Box 3)
    - 1966, Consumer magazine, 1 of 2 folders (Box 3)
    - 1966, Consumer magazine, 2 of 2 folders (Box 4)
    - 1966-1967, Consumer magazine (Box 4)
    - 1966, Consumer newspaper (Box 4)
    - 1966, Trade magazine, 4 folders (Box 4)
    - 1967, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - 1967-1968, Consumer magazine (Box 4)
    - 1967, Consumer newspaper (Box 4)
    - 1967, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - 1968-1969, Consumer newspaper (Box 4)
    - 1968, Trade magazine, 4 folders (Box 4)
    - 1969, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - 1969-1971, Consumer magazine (Box 5)
    - 1969, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 5)
    - 1970, Trade magazine (Box 5)
    - 1970-1971, Trade magazine (Box 5)
  - American Express (See also Oversize box OV1)
    - 1949-1951, Consumer magazine (Box 5)
    - 1949-1958, Consumer newspaper (Box 5)
    - 1949-1951, Trade magazine (Box 5)
    - 1952-1953, Consumer magazine (Box 5)
    - 1952-1953, Trade magazine (Box 6)
    - 1953-1962, Trade newspaper (Box 6)
    - 1954-1956, Consumer magazine (Box 6)
    - 1954-1957, Trade magazine (Box 6)
    - 1957-1959, Consumer magazine (Box 6)
    - 1958-1960, Trade magazine (Box 6)
    - 1959-1960, Consumer newspaper (Box 6)
    - 1960, Consumer magazine (Box 7)
    - 1961, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - 1961, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (Box 7)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine, 1 of 2 folders (Box 7)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine, 2 of 2 folders (Box 8)
    - 1962, Consumer newspaper (Box 8)
    - 1962, Trade magazine (Box 8)
  - American Motors (See also Oversize box OV1)
    - 1965, Consumer magazine (general) (Box 8)
    - 1965, Consumer magazine (Kelvinator) (Box 8)
    - 1965, Consumer newspaper (Box 8)
    - 1965, Trade magazine (Box 8)
    - 1966, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - 1966-1967, Trade magazine (general) (Box 8)
    - 1966, Trade magazine (Kelvinator) (Box 8)
    - 1966, Trade newspaper (Box 8)
    - 1967, Consumer magazine (Box 8)
    - 1967, Consumer newspaper (Box 8)
    - 1967, Trade magazine (Kelvinator) (Box 8)
  - AMF, Inc. (See also Oversize box OV1)
    - 1976-1980, Consumer magazine (boats) (Box 9)
    - 1976-1980, Consumer magazine (bowling products) (Box 9)
    - 1976-1980, Trade magazine (bowling products) (Box 9)
    - 1976-1980, Consumer magazine (fitness message) (Box 9)
    - 1976-1980, Consumer and trade magazine (mixed products) (Box 9)
    - 1980, Consumer magazine (tennis) (Box 9)
  - Arnold Bakers (See also Oversize box OV1)
    - 1948-1949, Consumer magazine (Box 9)
    - 1948-1949, Consumer and trade magazine (Box 9)
    - 1949-1951, Trade magazine (Box 9)
    - 1950-1952, Consumer magazine (Box 9)
    - 1950, Consumer newspaper (Box 9)
    - 1951-1952, Consumer newspaper (Box 9)
  - Association of American Railroads (See also Oversize box OV1)
    - 1946, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - 1946, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - 1946-1959, Trade newspaper (Box 10)
    - 1947, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - 1947, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - 1948, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - 1948, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 1949, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 1950, Consumer magazine (Box 11)
    - 1950, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 1951, Consumer magazine (Box 11)
    - 1951, Trade magazine (Box 11)
    - 1952, Consumer magazine (Box 11)
    - 1952, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine (Box 11)
    - 1953, Trade magazine (Box 11)
    - 1954, Consumer magazine (Box 11)
    - 1954, Trade magazine (Box 11)
    - 1955, Consumer magazine (Box 11)
    - 1955-1956, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 1957, Consumer magazine (Box 12)
    - 1957-1960, Trade magazine (Box 12)
    - 1959, Consumer magazine (Box 12)
    - 1960, Consumer magazine (Box 12)
  - AVCO Manufacturing Corp. (All advertising except for Crosley Division consumer products. See also Oversize box OV2)
    - 1949, Trade magazine (Spencer Heaters) (Box 12)
    - 1950-1951, Trade magazine (Box 12)
    - 1951, Consumer magazine (corporate) (Box 12)
    - 1952, Trade magazine (Spencer Heaters) (Box 12)
    - 1952, Trade magazine (Lycoming) (Box 12)
    - 1953-1954, Consumer newspaper (Box 12)
    - 1953-1954, Trade magazine (Spencer Heaters) (Box 12)
    - 1953, Trade magazine (Lycoming) (Box 12)
    - 1954, Trade magazine (Lycoming) (Box 12)
    - 1955, Consumer newspaper (corporate) (Box 12)
    - 1955, Trade magazine (Lycoming) (Box 12)
    - 1956, Consumer newspaper (Research and Advanced Development Division) (Box 12)
    - 1956, Consumer newspaper (Box 12)
    - 1956, Trade magazine (corporate) (Box 12)
    - 1956, Trade magazine (Research and Advanced Development Division), 2 folders (Box 13)
    - 1956, Trade magazine (Spencer Heaters) (Box 13)
    - 1956, Trade magazine (Lycoming) (Box 13)
    - 1957, Trade magazine (corporate) (Box 13)
    - 1957, Trade magazine (Crosley) (Box 13)
    - 1957, Trade magazine (Lycoming) (Box 13)
    - 1957, Trade magazine (Spencer Heaters) (Box 13)
    - 1958, Consumer magazine (Box 13)
    - 1958, Consumer newspaper (Box 13)
    - 1958, Trade magazine (corporate) (Box 13)
    - 1958, Trade magazine (Lycoming) (Box 13)
    - 1958, Trade magazine (Box 13)
    - 1959, Consumer magazine (corporate) (Box 13)
    - 1959, Consumer newspaper (corporate) (Box 13)
    - 1959, Trade magazine (corporate) (Box 13)
    - 1959, Trade magazine (Lycoming) (Box 13)
    - 1959, Trade magazine (Box 13)
    - 1960, Consumer magazine (corporate) (Box 14)
    - 1960, Consumer newspaper (Box 14)
    - 1960, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - 1961, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - 1961, Consumer newspaper (Box 14)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (corporate) (Box 14)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (Research and Advanced Development Division) (Box 14)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (Lycoming) (Box 14)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (Electronics and Ordnance Division) (Box 14)
    - 1961, Trade magazine (Nashville Division) (Box 14)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine (Box 14)
    - 1962, Trade magazine (corporate) (Box 14)
    - 1962, Trade magazine (Research and Advanced Development Division) (Box 14)
    - 1962, Trade magazine (Lycoming) (Box 14)
    - 1963, Consumer magazine (Box 14)
    - 1963, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - 1964, Consumer magazine (Box 14)
    - 1964, Consumer newspaper (Box 14)
    - 1964, Trade magazine (Box 14)
    - 1965, Consumer magazine (Box 14)
    - 1965, Trade magazine (Box 14)
  - AVCO-Crosley Consumer Products (See also Oversize boxes OV2-OV3)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine (Shelvador), 2 folders (Box 15)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine (radios) (Box 15)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine (ranges) (Box 15)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine (freezers) (Box 15)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine (Box 15)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine (televisions) (Box 15)
    - 1949, Consumer newspaper (Box 15)
    - 1949, Trade magazine (multiple products) (Box 15)
    - 1949, Trade magazine (Box 15)
    - 1949-1951, Trade newspaper (Box 15)
    - 1950, Consumer magazine (Shelvador) (Box 15)
    - 1950, Consumer magazine, 1-3 of 4 folders (Box 15)
    - 1950, Consumer magazine, 4 of 4 folders (Box 16)
    - 1950, Consumer newspaper (televisions) (Box 16)
    - 1950, Consumer newspaper (radios) (Box 16)
    - 1950, Consumer newspaper (Box 16)
    - 1950, Trade magazine (Box 16)
    - 1951, Consumer magazine (Shelvador) (Box 16)
    - 1951, Consumer magazine (Box 16)
    - 1951, Consumer newspaper (Shelvador), 2 folders (Box 16)
    - 1951, Consumer newspaper (televisions), 1-3 of 5 folders (Box 16)
    - 1951, Consumer newspaper, 4-5 of 5 folders (Box 17)
    - 1951, Trade magazine (Box 17)
    - 1952, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 17)
    - 1952, Consumer newspaper (Shelvador) (Box 17)
    - 1952, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - 1952, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - 1952, Trade newspaper (Box 17)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine (Shelvador), 2 folders (Box 17)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine (washer/dryer) (Box 17)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine (kitchens), 2 folders (Box 18)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine (air conditioners) (Box 18)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine (ranges) (Box 18)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine (refrigerator/freezers) (Box 18)
    - 1953, Consumer magazine (Box 18)
    - 1953, Consumer newspaper (Shelvador) (Box 18)
    - 1953, Consumer newspaper (washer/dryer) (Box 18)
    - 1953, Consumer newspaper, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - 1953, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - 1953, Trade newspaper (Box 19)
    - 1954, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 19)
    - 1954, Consumer newspaper (Box 19)
    - 1954, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - 1955, Consumer magazine (Box 19)
    - 1955, Trade magazine (Box 19)
  - Bellows and Company: See National Distillers Products (Box 19)
  - Benton and Bowles (See also Oversize box OV3)
    - 1952-1958, Trade magazine (Box 20)
    - 1953-1980, Consumer magazine (Box 20)
    - 1958-1959, Trade magazine (Box 20)
    - 1959-1975, Trade newspaper (Box 20)
    - 1960-1963, Trade magazine (Box 20)
    - 1962-1967, Consumer newspaper (Box 20)
    - 1971-1976, Trade magazine (Box 20)
    - 1977-1980, Trade magazine (Box 20)
  - Best Foods (See also Oversize boxes OV3-OV4)
    - Corporate and multiple product
      - 1938-1951, Consumer magazine (Box 20)
      - 1938-1944, Consumer newspaper (Box 20)
      - 1942-1946, Trade magazine (Box 20)
      - 1943-1951, Trade newspaper (Box 20)
      - 1946-1949, Consumer newspaper (Box 20)
      - 1947-1951, Trade magazine (Box 20)
      - 1951, Consumer newspaper (Box 20)
    - Hellman's Mayonnaise
      - 1933, Consumer newspaper, 4 folders (Box 21)
      - 1933-1941, Trade magazine (Box 21)
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - 1935-1936, Consumer newspaper (Box 21)
      - 1936-1937, Consumer magazine (Box 21)
      - 1936, Consumer newspaper (Box 21)
      - 1937, Consumer newspaper (Box 21)
      - 1938, Consumer magazine (Box 21)
      - 1938, Consumer newspaper (Box 21)
      - 1939-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 21)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Box 21)
      - 1940, Consumer newspaper (Box 21)
      - 1942-1944, Consumer magazine (Box 22)
      - 1942-1944, Trade magazine (Box 22)
      - 1943-1946, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 22)
      - 1944, Consumer newspaper (Box 22)
      - 1945-1947, Consumer magazine (Box 22)
      - 1945-1947, Consumer newspaper (Box 22)
      - 1945-1951, Trade magazine (Box 22)
      - 1948, Consumer magazine (Box 22)
      - 1948, Consumer newspaper (Box 22)
      - 1949-1951, Consumer magazine (Box 22)
      - 1949, Consumer newspaper (Box 22)
      - 1951-1952, Consumer newspaper (Box 22)
    - Nucoa oleomargarine
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - 1935, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - 1935-1937, Trade magazine (Box 23)
      - 1936, Consumer magazine (Box 23)
      - 1936-1937, Consumer newspaper (Box 23)
      - 1937-1938, Consumer magazine (Box 23)
      - 1938-1941, Consumer newspaper (Box 23)
      - 1938, Trade magazine (Box 23)
      - 1939-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 23)
      - 1939-1940, Trade magazine (Box 24)
      - 1941, Consumer magazine (Box 24)
      - 941, Trade magazine (Box 24)
      - 1942-1943, Consumer magazine (Box 24)
      - 1942, Consumer newspaper (Box 24)
      - 1942, Trade magazine (Box 24)
      - 1943, Consumer newspaper (Box 24)
      - 1943, Trade magazine (Box 24)
      - 1944-1946, Consumer magazine (Box 24)
      - 1944, Consumer newspaper (Box 24)
      - 1944, Trade magazine (Box 24)
      - 1945, Consumer newspaper (Box 24)
      - 1945, Trade magazine (Box 25)
      - 1946-1947, Consumer newspaper (Box 25)
      - 1946, Trade magazine (Box 25)
      - 1947, Consumer magazine (Box 25)
      - 1947-1951, Trade magazine (Box 25)
      - 1951, Consumer magazine (Box 25)
      - 1951, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Standard Milling
      - 1934, Consumer newspaper (Box 25)
      - 1935, Consumer newspaper (Box 25)
      - 1936-1945, Consumer magazine (Box 25)
      - 1936, Consumer newspaper (Box 25)
      - 1937-1938, Consumer newspaper (Box 25)
      - 1945-1946, Consumer and trade magazine (Box 26)
      - 1945, Consumer and trade newspaper, 3 folders (Box 26)
      - 1946, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - 1946-1947, Consumer newspaper (Box 26)
      - 1947-1949, Consumer magazine (Box 26)
      - 1948-1950, Consumer newspaper (Box 26)
    - Various condiments (Sandwich Spread, French dressing, Mustard with horseradish)
      - 1936-1944, Consumer newspaper (Box 26)
      - 1939-1943, Consumer magazine (Box 26)
      - 1944-1946, Consumer and trade newspaper (Box 26)
      - 1945-1951, Consumer newspaper (Box 26)
      - 1947-1951, Consumer magazine (Box 26)
    - Various shoe polish (Shinola, Bixby Jet Oil, Two-in-One, Tuxedo)
      - 1939, Consumer and trade magazine (Box 27)
      - 1939-1940, Consumer newspaper (Box 27)
      - 1940, Consumer and trade magazine (Box 27)
      - 1946, Consumer magazine (Box 27)
      - 1946-1947, Consumer magazine (Box 27)
      - 1946, Consumer newspaper (Box 27)
      - 1946, Trade magazine (Box 27)
  - Bituminous Coal Institute (See also Oversize box OV4)
    - 1943-1945, Consumer magazine (Box 27)
    - 1944-1945, Consumer newspaper (Box 27)
    - 1944-1945, Trade magazine (Box 27)
    - 1944-1945, Trade newspaper (Box 27)
    - 1945, Consumer magazine (Box 27)
    - 1945, Consumer magazine (Box 27)
    - 1946, Consumer magazine (Box 28)
    - 1946-1952, Consumer newspaper (Box 28)
    - 1946, Trade magazine (Box 28)
    - 1946-1948, Trade newspaper (Box 28)
    - 1947, Consumer magazine (Box 28)
    - 1947, Trade magazine (Box 28)
    - 1948, Consumer magazine (Box 28)
    - 1948, Trade magazine (Box 28)
    - 1949, Consumer magazine (Box 28)
    - 1949-1950, Trade magazine (Box 28)
    - 1950, Consumer magazine (Box 28)
    - 1951, Consumer magazine (Box 28)
    - 1951, Trade magazine (Box 28)
    - 1952-1953, Consumer magazine (Box 28)
    - 1952, Trade magazine (Box 28)
    - 1953, Trade magazine (Box 28)
    - 1954, Trade magazine (Box 28)
  - Bristol Myers (See also Oversize box OV4)
    - 1934, Consumer newspaper (Box 29)
    - 1934, Trade magazine (Sal Hepatica) (Box 29)
    - 1934, Trade magazine (Rubberset brushes) (Box 29)
    - 1935, Consumer magazine (Sal Hepatica) (Box 29)
    - 1935, Consumer newspaper (Box 29)
    - 1935, Trade magazine (Sal Hepatica), 2 folders (Box 29)
    - 1935, Trade magazine (Rubberset brushes) (Box 29)
  - Calvert Distillers Corporation (See also Oversize box OV4)
    - 1937, Consumer magazine (Box 29)
    - 1937, Consumer magazine (Special and Reserve whiskey), 4 folders (Box 29)
    - 1937, Consumer newspaper (Old Drum whiskey) (Box 30)
    - 1937, Consumer newspaper (Box 30)
    - 1937, Trade magazine (Box 30)
    - 1937, Trade newspaper (Box 30)
    - 1938, Consumer magazine (Box 30)
    - 1938, Consumer newspaper (Special and Reserve whiskey), 2 folders (Box 30)
    - 1938, Consumer newspaper (Box 31)
    - 1938-1940, Trade magazine (Box 31)
    - 1939, Consumer magazine (Box 31)
    - 1939-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 31)
    - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Old Drum whiskey) (Box 31)
    - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Box 31)
    - 1939-1940, Consumer newspaper (Box 31)
    - 1939-1940, Trade magazine (Box 31)
    - 1960, Consumer magazine (Box 31)
    - 1960, Consumer newspaper (Box 31)
  - Can Manufacturers' Institute (See also Oversize box OV4)
    - 1943-1944, Consumer magazine (Box 32)
    - 1944, Consumer magazine (Box 32)
    - 1944, Consumer newspaper (Box 32)
    - 1944, Trade magazine (Box 32)
    - 1944-1945, Trade newspaper (Box 32)
    - 1945, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - 1945, Consumer newspaper (Box 32)
    - 1945, Trade magazine, 4 folders (Box 32)
    - 1946, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - 1946-1948, Consumer newspaper (Box 33)
    - 1946, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - 1946, Trade newspaper (Box 33)
    - 1948, Consumer magazine (Box 33)
    - 1948, Trade magazine (Box 33)
    - 1949, Trade magazine (Box 33)
  - Carling Brewing Company (See also Oversize box OV4)
    - 1950-1952, Consumer magazine (Box 33)
    - 1950-1953, Consumer newspaper (Box 33)
    - 1952-1957, Trade magazine (Box 33)
    - 1953-1955, Consumer magazine (Box 33)
    - 1954-1959, Consumer newspaper (Box 33)
    - 1959-1960, Consumer magazine (Box 33)
  - Chemical Bank/New York Trust Company (See also Oversize box OV4)
    - 1960-1961, Trade magazine, 3 folders (Box 34)
    - 1961, Consumer magazine (Box 34)
    - 1961-1965, Consumer newspaper (Box 34)
    - 1965-1967, Trade newspaper (Box 34)
    - 1962, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 34)
    - 1962, Trade magazine (Box 34)
    - 1963, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - 1963, Trade magazine (Box 34)
    - 1964, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - 1964, Trade magazine (Box 34)
    - 1965, Consumer magazine, 4 folders (Box 35)
    - 1965, Trade magazine (Box 35)
    - 1966, Consumer magazine, 5 folders (Box 35)
    - 1966, Consumer newspaper, 3 folders (Box 35)
    - 1966, Trade magazine (Box 35)
    - 1967, Consumer magazine, 1-4 of 8 folders (Box 35)
    - 1967, Consumer newspaper, 5-8 of 8 folders (Box 36)
    - 1967, Trade magazine (Box 36)
    - 1968, Consumer magazine, 3 folders (Box 36)
    - 1968, Trade magazine (Box 36)
    - 1968-1974, Trade newspaper (Box 36)
    - 1969, Consumer magazine (Box 36)
    - 1969-1974, Consumer newspaper (Box 36)
    - 1969, Trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - 1970-1972, Consumer magazine (Box 36)
    - 1970-1974, Trade magazine (Box 36)
    - 1973-1974, Consumer magazine (Box 36)
  - Colgate-Palmolive-Peet Company (See also Oversize box OV5)
    - Corporate and multiple product
      - 1935-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 37)
      - 1935, Consumer newspaper (Box 37)
      - 1935, Trade magazine (Box 37)
      - 1936, Consumer newspaper (all-color comics), 2 folders (Box 37)
      - 1936, Trade magazine (Box 37)
      - 1937-1938, Consumer newspaper (Box 37)
      - 1937, Trade magazine (Box 37)
      - 1937-1940, Trade newspaper (Box 37)
      - 1938, Consumer newspaper (all-color comics), 2 folders (Box 37)
      - 1938, Trade magazine (Box 37)
      - 1939-1940, Consumer newspaper (Box 37)
      - 1939-1940, Trade magazine (Box 37)
    - Cashmere Bouquet
      - 1935, Consumer magazine (Box 38)
      - 1935-1937, Trade magazine (Box 38)
      - 1936, Consumer magazine (Box 38)
      - 1937, Consumer magazine (Box 38)
      - 1937-1940, Consumer newspaper (Box 38)
      - 1937-1940, Trade magazine (Box 38)
      - 1938, Consumer magazine (Box 38)
      - 1939, Consumer magazine (Box 38)
    - Colgate Dental Cream and Powder
      - 1935, Consumer and trade magazine, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - 1935, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - 1936, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - 1936, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - 1937, Consumer magazine, 2 folders (Box 39)
      - 1937, Consumer magazine (Box 39)
      - 1937, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 39)
      - 1938, Consumer magazine (Box 39)
      - 1938, Consumer newspaper (Box 39)
      - 1938-1939, Consumer magazine (Box 39)
      - 1939-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 39)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper, 3 folders (Box 39)
      - 1940, Consumer magazine (Box 39)
      - 1940, Consumer newspaper (Box 39)
      - 1940-1941, Consumer newspaper (Box 39)
    - Palmolive Soap
      - 1935, Trade magazine (Box 40)
      - 1935-1936, Trade magazine (Measured Soap) (Box 40)
      - 1936, Consumer magazine (Box 40)
      - 1936, Consumer newspaper (Box 40)
      - 1936-1937, Trade magazine (Box 40)
      - 1937, Consumer magazine (Box 40)
      - 1937, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 40)
      - 1937-1940, Trade magazine (Measured Soap) (Box 40)
      - 1938, Consumer magazine (Box 40)
      - 1938, Consumer newspaper, 2 folders (Box 40)
      - 1938-1940, Trade magazine (Box 40)
      - 1939, Consumer magazine (Box 40)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper (Box 41)
      - 1939-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 41)
      - 1940, Consumer newspaper (Box 41)
    - Super Suds/Klek
      - 1935-1936, Consumer newspaper (Box 41)
      - 1935-1940, Trade magazine (Box 41)
      - 1936-1939, Consumer magazine (Box 41)
      - 1937, Consumer newspaper, 4 folders (Box 41)
      - 1937, Consumer newspaper (Box 41)
      - 1938, Consumer newspaper (Box 41)
      - 1939, Consumer newspaper, 3 folders (Box 41)
      - 1939-1940, Consumer magazine (Box 42)
      - 1939-1941, Consumer newspaper (Box 42)
    - Various shaving products
      - 1935-1936, Consumer magazine (Box 42)